{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "James Hanna",
      "description": "first deck",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "second deck",
      "description": "lol",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "third Short Deck",
      "description": "Hello",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "first card",
      "back": "first back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "fourth card",
      "back": "fourth back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "another card",
      "back": "another back",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "next card",
      "back": "next back",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "one more",
      "back": "like",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "once ju",
      "back": "5",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "First Card",
      "back": "Yo",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "Second Card",
      "back": "Still Not Enough",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "sixth card",
      "back": "sixth back",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "another card",
      "back": "another back",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "adding a card",
      "back": "testing",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 13
    }
  ]
}